Guide to the Thomas Michlovic Papers, 1978-2002 AIS.2002.04
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Greater Pittsburgh Convention and Visitors Bureau
  - Tourism-Making Gr. Pittsburgh A Leading Destination For World Visitors, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Regional Renaissance Partnership, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - GPCVB Board Meeting Minutes, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Retreat at Oglebay, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Working Together Consortium – Tourism Marketing Committee, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - GPCVB Board Meeting Minutes, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - GPCVB Board Meeting Minutes, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - GPCVB Board Meeting Minutes, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - GPCVB Board Retreat Strategic Planning, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 11)
- World Trade Center of Pittsburgh
  - By-Laws, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Board Meeting Minutes, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Board Meeting Minutes, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - International Fair, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Board Meeting Minutes, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Allegheny County Threat to Decertify World Trade Center, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Board Meeting Minutes, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Board Meeting Minutes, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 21)
- Mon Valley Initiative
  - Mon Valley Initiative Controversy, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Survey of Mon Valley Municipalities (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Lending Report, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - MVI Retreat, January 10, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - MVI Correspondence and Board Meeting Minutes (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Mon Valley Initiative Community Investment Fund Committee
  - Statement of Purpose (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - CIF Board Meeting Minutes, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - CIF Board Meeting Minutes, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - CIF Board Meeting Minutes, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - CIF Board Meeting Minutes, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - CIF Board Meeting Minutes, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - CIF Board Meeting Minutes, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - CIF Board Meeting Minutes, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - CIF Board Meeting Minutes, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Pensions
  - COLA - State School PERS correspondence and background, 1999-2001 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - School Employee Retirement (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - 2000 Discussion – Draft Legislation – HB 2868 – Press Releases, News Articles (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - SERS Pension – HB 223 – Correspondence, Memos, Press Releases (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Amendment 614 to HB 27 of 2001 (Never Introduced) Analysis and Background (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - SERS – Teachers Pension HB 1513 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Retirement changes HB 26 of 2001 – Co-sponsorship Memo, Bill and Co-sponsors (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Municipal Pension Funds – 3rd Class Cities, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Firefighters Early Pension – HB 778, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Local Government Pension Report, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 10)
- Stormwater Management and Water Restoration
  - Stormwater Management Legislation introduced by Tom Michlovic (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Stormwater Management Correspondence, 1987-1990 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Stormwater Management Act – Poison Runoff, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Stormwater Management Testimony, July 15, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Water Restoration (related to underground mining), 1982-1993 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Water Restoration Legislation, 1987, 1989, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Water Restoration – Testimony, Articles and Hearings (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - 3 Rivers Wet Weather Demonstration Program – Eastern Communities Basin Group (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Turtle Creek Watershed (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Turtle Creek Basin – US Army Corps Engineers Report Summary (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Wetlands (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - 1996 Flood Recovery (Box 15, Folder 22)
- Steel Industry Heritage Corporation (SIHC)
  - SIHC Board Meeting Minutes, 1988-1989 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - SIHC Board Meeting Minutes, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - SIHC Board Meeting Minutes, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - SIHC Board Meeting Minutes, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - SIHC Board Meeting Minutes, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - SIHC Board Meeting Minutes, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - SIHC Board Meeting Minutes, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - SIHC Board Meeting Minutes, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - SIHC Board Meeting Minutes, 1998 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - SIHC Board Meeting Minutes, 1999 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - SIHC Board Meeting Minutes, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - SIHC Board Meeting Minutes, 2001 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - "Rivers of Steel" Brochure (Box 16, Folder 13)
- Braddock's Field Historical Society (BFHS)
  - BFHS Newsletters, 1981-2001 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - BFHS Preamble – Bylaws and Revisions (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Background Information on 1755 Braddock Expedition (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Ambrose Consulting & Training (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - BFHS Correspondence, 1978, 1980-1983, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - BFHS Board Minutes and Correspondence, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - BFHS Board Minutes and Correspondence, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - BFHS Board Minutes and Correspondence, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - BFHS Board Minutes and Correspondence, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - BFHS Board Minutes and Correspondence, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - BFHS Board Minutes and Correspondence, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - BFHS Board Minutes and Correspondence, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - BFHS Board Minutes and Correspondence, 1994 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - BFHS Board Minutes and Correspondence, 1995 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - BFHS Board Minutes and Correspondence, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - BFHS Board Minutes and Correspondence, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 1-2)
  - BFHS Board Minutes and Correspondence, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 3-5)
  - BFHS Board Minutes and Correspondence, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 6-8)
  - BFHS Board Minutes and Correspondence, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 9-10)
  - BFHS Board Minutes and Correspondence, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 11)
- Steel Valley Authority
  - Steel Valley Authority Final Report of Economic Development Employment Survey (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Steel Valley Authority - Reclaiming The Industrial Heartland (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Steel Valley Authority Board Minutes and Correspondence, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Steel Valley Authority Board Minutes and Correspondence, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Steel Valley Authority Economic Development Employment Survey Narrative Responses, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Steel Valley Authority City Pride Bakery Business Plan, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Steel Valley Authority Board Minutes and Correspondence, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Steel Valley Authority Board Minutes and Correspondence, 1991 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Steel Valley Authority Board Minutes and Correspondence, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Steel Valley Authority Board Minutes and Correspondence, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Steel Valley Authority Board Minutes and Correspondence, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Steel Valley Authority Board Minutes and Correspondence, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Steel Valley Authority Board Minutes and Correspondence, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Steel Valley Authority Board Minutes and Correspondence, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Steel Valley Authority Board Minutes and Correspondence, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Steel Valley Authority Board Minutes and Correspondence, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Steel Valley Authority Environmental Assessment and Community Involvement in the Lower Monongahela River Valley, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Steel Valley Authority Board Minutes and Correspondence, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 18)
- Labor
  - Steel Plant Shutdowns (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Fulton Theater and Local #3, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - WABCO Proposal (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - WABCO Greensburg Plant (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Precise Technologies - UE Local #645 (Box 19, Folder 23)
- Regional Economic Revitalization Initiative
  - CMU - Regional Economic Revitalization Initiative, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 24)
- Private Industry Council
  - Private Industry Council, 1988-1990 (Box 19, Folder 25)
- Southwestern Pennsylvania Regional Planning Commission (SPRPC)
  - SPRPC Regional Transportation Plan, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - SPRPC Retreat, 1988 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - SPRPC Correspondence, 1988-1991 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - SPRPC Conference, 1991 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - State Representative Tom Michlovic's Testimony to Transportation Commission and SPRPC, 1995 and 1999 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - SPRPC Mon-Valley Highways (Box 20, Folder 6)
- Highway Budget
  - Correspondence, 1979-1980 (Box 20, Folder 7)
- Westinghouse Bridge
  - Bridge Rehabilitation, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 8)
- Port Authority of Allegheny County
  - Port Authority Correspondence (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Port Authority - Busway East (Box 20, Folder 10)
- Tri-Boro Connector
  - Tri-Boro Connector – Communities of Turtle Creek, East Pittsburgh and Wilmerding – Correspondence (Box 20, Folder 11)
- Railroads
  - Railroad Right-of-Way and Historical Railroads (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Union Railroad – Braddock and Rankin – and Sale of Property (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Rails-To-Trails (Box 20, Folder 14)
- Port of Pittsburgh Commission
  - Port of Pittsburgh Commission Correspondence (Box 20, Folder 15)
- Mon River Lock and Dam Replacement
  - Mon River Lock and Dam Replacement Correspondence (Box 20, Folder 16)
- Competitive Pittsburgh Task Force
  - Competitive Pittsburgh Task Force Correspondence (Box 20, Folder 17)
- Environment
  - Coal Strip Mining Allegations - Thornburgh Administration, 1982 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Three Mile Island (Box 20, Folder 19)
- Mon Valley Commission
  - Mon Valley Commission Meeting Minutes and Correspondence, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Mon Valley Commission Meeting Minutes and Correspondence, 1988 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Mon Valley Commission Meeting Minutes and Correspondence, 1989 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Mon Valley Commission Meeting Minutes and Correspondence, 1990 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Mon Valley Commission Meeting Minutes and Correspondence, 1991 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Mon Valley Commission Meeting Minutes and Correspondence, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Mon Valley Commission Meeting Minutes and Correspondence, 1993 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Mon Valley Commission Meeting Minutes and Correspondence, 1994 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Mon Valley Commission Meeting Minutes and Correspondence, 1995 (Box 20, Folder 28)
- AIDS Legislation
  - AIDS Legislation and Correspondence, 1993 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - AIDS Task Force and Shepard Wellness Community (Box 20, Folder 30)
- Gay and Lesbian Task Force
  - Gay and Lesbian Task Force Correspondence (Box 20, Folder 31)
- Education
  - Distressed Schools Hearing – Duquesne School District and Clairton School District, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Philadelphia School district Bail-out – HB 1289, 2002 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Special Education, HB 996 of 2001 and Special Education Inclusion, HB 933 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - School District of Pittsburgh (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - McKeesport Area School District (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - East Allegheny School District (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Woodland Hills School District (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Vouchers, HB 1655 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Educational Empowerment Act, SB 652 of 2000 (Act 16) (Box 21, Folder 9)
- Vietnam Veteran's Leadership Program (VVLP)
  - VVLP Mission Statement and Accomplishments, 1994-1997 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - VVLP Meeting Minutes and Correspondence, 1988, 1990, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - VVLP Board Meeting Minutes, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - VVLP Board Meeting Minutes, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - VVLP Board Meeting Minutes, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - VVLP Board Meeting Minutes, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - VVLP Board Meeting Minutes, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 16)
- Mon Valley Job Center Task Force
  - Mon Valley Job Center Task Force Correspondence, 1989-1991 (Box 21, Folder 17)
- The New Eastland Mall and Market Place, North Versailles
  - Eastland Mall and Market Place Correspondence, 1988-1991 (Box 21, Folder 18)
- Eastern Area Adult Services - Turtle Creek
  - Eastern Area Adult Services, Turtle Creek Correspondence (Box 21, Folder 19)
- Housing and Homeless Providers
  - Housing and Homeless Providers Correspondence (Box 21, Folder 20)
- Westinghouse Valley Human Services Center, Turtle Creek
  - Westinghouse Valley Human Services Center Correspondence (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Westinghouse Valley Human Services Center vs. Commissioner Crammer (Box 21, Folder 22)
- Greater Pittsburgh Literacy Council
  - Greater Pittsburgh Literacy Council Correspondence (Box 21, Folder 23)
- Golden Triangle Council of the Blind
  - Golden Triangle Council of the Blind, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 24)
- The Harrisburg Report
  - Harrisburg Report - Tom's Television Show from Harrisburg (Box 21, Folder 25)
- Local Government Committee
  - Representative Michlovic's Testimony to Local Government Committee Regarding Changes to Act 170, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 26)
- Kane Hospital
  - Privatization of Kane Hospital, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 27)
- Ladies of the Grand Army of the Republic Home
  - Ladies of the Grand Army of the Republic Home, Swissvale - Correspondence (Box 21, Folder 28)
- Hays Sound Stage
  - Hays Sound Stage Correspondence (Box 21, Folder 29)
- Pennsylvania Council on the Arts
  - Pennsylvania Council on the Arts Correspondence (Box 21, Folder 30)
- Pittsburgh Cultural Trust
  - Pittsburgh Cultural Trust Correspondence (Box 21, Folder 31)
- Steffi Domike Film Company
  - Steffi Domike Film Company Correspondence (Box 21, Folder 32)
- Pitcairn Borough
  - Pitcairn Flood Aftermath Report, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 33)
  - Pitcairn Railyards Proposal - Racetrack, 1980-1981 (Box 21, Folder 34)
- Enterprise Zone Corporation of Braddock
  - Enterprise Zone Mission Statements (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Enterprise Zone Minutes and Correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Enterprise Zone Minutes and Correspondence, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Enterprise Zone Minutes and Correspondence, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Enterprise Zone Minutes and Correspondence, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Enterprise Zone Minutes and Correspondence, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Enterprise Zone Minutes and Correspondence, 1992 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Enterprise Zone Minutes and Correspondence, 1993 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Enterprise Zone Minutes and Correspondence, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Enterprise Zone Minutes and Correspondence, 1995 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Enterprise Zone Minutes and Correspondence, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Enterprise Zone Minutes and Correspondence, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Enterprise Zone Minutes and Correspondence, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Enterprise Zone Minutes and Correspondence, 1999-2000 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Enterprise Zone Minutes and Correspondence, 2001 (Box 22, Folder 15)
- Pro-Choice Legislation
  - Pro Choice / Abortion Issue Correspondence and Information (Box 22, Folder 16)
- Allegheny County
  - Allegheny County Access Program (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Allegheny County Planning Department (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Allegheny County Redevelopment Department (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Allegheny County Airport Midfield Terminal (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Allegheny County Housing Development Corporation (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Allegheny County Housing Authority (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Allegheny County Community College (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Allegheny County Community College / Braddock Campus (Box 22, Folder 24)
- Allegheny Recovery Corporation
  - Allegheny Recovery Corporation - Duquesne Steel Site (Box 22, Folder 25)
- The Ben Franklin Partnership Program
  - The Ben Franklin Partnership Program Correspondence (Box 22, Folder 26)
- Common Cause
  - Common Cause Correspondence (Box 22, Folder 27)
- Citizens League
  - Citizens League Correspondence (Box 22, Folder 28)
- Animal Care and Welfare
  - Animal Care and Welfare Correspondence (Box 22, Folder 29)
- Rochez Rubber Recovery Project
  - Rochez Rubber Recovery Company Correspondence (Box 22, Folder 30)
- Mon Yough Chamber of Commerce
  - Mon Yough Chamber of Commerce Correspondence (Box 22, Folder 31)
- Welfare Reform
  - Welfare Reform - Meetings and Seminars, 1992-1999 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Welfare Reform - SB 1441 of 1995, 1996 and HB 1392 of 1993 - Legislation, Votes, Amendments and Talking Points, 1993-1996 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Welfare Reform - Correspondence and Organizations, 1992-1996 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Welfare Reform - Grant Assistance and Aid to Families with Dependent Children Lists, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Welfare Reform - Michlovic letter to House Members, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Welfare Reform Issue Information (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Welfare Reform - Governor Casey's Task Force to Reduce Welfare Dependency Final Report, 1993 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Welfare Reform - House Republicans Proposal Dependence to Dignity Freedom from Welfare, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Welfare Reform Reports (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Welfare Reform - Medical Assistance Changes for Detoxification of Patients - Personal Notes and Correspondence, 1993-1995 (Box 23, Folder 10)
- Local Initiatives Support Corporation
  - Local Initiatives Support Corporation Correspondence (Box 23, Folder 11)
- Allegheny County Municipal Tours
  - Municipal Tours of 35th District Communities, 1980-1995 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Distressed Municipalities List (Box 23, Folder 13)
- Liquor Control Board
  - Act 47 - Liquor Code Changes (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Guest Editorial Regarding Sale of State Stores, October 28, 1996 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Privatizing State Liquor Stores (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Nuisance Bar Program, 2001 (Box 23, Folder 17)
- Crime
  - Regional Police Network, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Corrections Officers Retirement, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - House Committee Hearing on Crime, 1994 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Crime Conference, May 5-6, 1994 (Box 23, Folder 21)
- Mon Valley Revitalization
  - Mon Valley Revitalization - Correspondence and Report (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Mon Valley Strategic Growth Plan Phase I, 1995 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Mon Valley Strategic Growth Plan Phase III, 1996 (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Mon Valley Revitalization Project Meeting, December 12, 1994 (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - Mon Valley Revitalization Renaissance Funding (Box 23, Folder 26)
- Michlovic Proposed Legislation
  - Lobbyist Disclosure Act and Regulations (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Legislative Data Processing Committee, 1997-2002 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Municipal Dissolution Legislation (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - HB 754 – Tire Fires (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Flood Damaged Vehicles Legislation (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Surcharge for Abandoned Industrial Sites Assessment Fund Legislation (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - HB 1455 – Veteran's Preference, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - HB 2071 – Auto Reform (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - HB 2071 – Regulating Insurance Rates and Testimony to HB 2072, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - HB 2355 - 1% Sales Tax, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - FERC Order 636 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - HB 226 – Bingo Licensing, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - HB 1709 – Senior Citizen Rebate, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - HB 1515 – 2nd Class County Assessments (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - HB 225 – Anthrax Vaccine, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - HR 112 – Lennie Lenape Coalition (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - HR 207 – Federal Funding VA Medical Program (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - HR 526 – LIHEAP Regulation (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - HB 1463 – McKeesport Deed Conveyance – Act 66 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - HR 192 – Buy American Month, July, 1997 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - HB 23 – Storm Water Management (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Flood Control and Sewage Treatments (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence – Turtle Creek Flood Control, 1991 (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - Health Care Transition Fund Amending SB 1583 (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - County Jail Amending HB 2116 (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - HB 1069 – Definition of Correction Officers, 1985 (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - HB 363 – Forensic Unit Pension, 1989 (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - HB 328 – Forensic Unit Early Pension, 1989 (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - Employee Ownership Task Force (Box 24, Folder 29)
- Campaigns
  - The Harrisburg Report (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Sample Publicity (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Samples of "The Report To The People" (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Literature "Primer of Taxonomics" (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Speeches – Memorial Day and Veteran's Day (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Michlovic Awards (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Gwen and Tom Michlovic Christmas Cards (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - 1989 Campaign and Elections Workshop – Washington D.C. (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Election, 1976 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Election, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Election, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Election, 1982 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Election, 1984 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Election, 1986 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Election, 1988 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Election, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Election, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Election, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Election, 1994 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Election, 1996 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Election, 1998 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Election, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Election questionnaires and endorsements (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - Campaign layouts by Vic Wilem (deceased) (Box 25, Folder 24)
- Correspondence
  - MH/MR Correspondence – Philadelphia/Pittsburgh, 1990-1992 (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - MH/MR Allegheny County Budget Hearings, 1994 (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - Penn State McKeesport Board, 1997-1999 (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - Rotary Youth Leadership (Box 25, Folder 28)
  - Rotary "Operation Kidshot" (Box 25, Folder 29)
  - Wacko File (Box 25, Folder 30)
- Gun Control and Assault Weapons
  - Michlovic's Amendments HB 185 - "Preemption of Local and State Gun Bans" (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Governor's Assault Weapons Proposal (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Firearms Mental Health Check (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Gun Safety, 1999 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Assault Weapons List and Photos (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Assault Weapons Database Report/Types of Weapons (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Background Information (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Michlovic's Testimony and Testimony of Others (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Legislation (Box 26, Folder 10)
- House of Representatives
  - Rules Reform Group (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Leadership Candidates and Seniority System, 1996 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Leadership Campaign, 1998 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Committee Assignment Requests, 1985-1993 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Committee Assignment Requests, 1995-1998 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Political Scandals (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Telecommunications Committee, 1991-1992 (Box 26, Folder 17)
- Correspondence
  - Medical Malpractice (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Health Insurance (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - MH/MR Health Insurance (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Drug and Alcohol (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Labor Issues (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - General Contractors Issues (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - PUC Issues (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Community Issues (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Family Issues (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Education Issues (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - School of Choice/Vouchers (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Animal Issues (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Food Bank Issues (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Riverboat Gambling and Slots at Racetracks (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Real Estate Disclosure (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Public Drinking Water (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Transportation Issues (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Insurance Issues (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Allegheny County – Sales Tax, Regional Renaissance and Home Rule Charter (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Allegheny County Tax Assessments (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Various Issues (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - East Busway (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Mon Valley Expressway (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Mon Valley Expressway – Litigation, 1994 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Mon Valley Expressway – Mayor Murphy and Pitt Law Clinic (Box 28, Folder 4)